<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
 This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site.
 It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content.
 You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another.
 This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site.

 To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps:
 1. Log in to that site as an administrator.
 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel.
 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list.
 4. Activate & Run Importer.
 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page.
 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users
    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an
    existing user on the site or to create a new user.
 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc.
    contained in this file into your site.
-->
<!-- generator="WordPress.com" created="2023-05-29 14:03"-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/">
  <channel>
<title>Quantum Computing</title>
<link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com</link>
<description/>
<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 14:03:48 +0000</pubDate>
<language>en</language>
<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
<wp:base_site_url>http://wordpress.com/</wp:base_site_url>
<wp:base_blog_url>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com</wp:base_blog_url>
<wp:author>
  <wp:author_id>235504971</wp:author_id>
  <wp:author_login>payaldayanand26</wp:author_login>
  <wp:author_email>payaldayanand26@gmail.com</wp:author_email>
  <wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[Payal Dayanand]]></wp:author_display_name>
  <wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[Payal]]></wp:author_first_name>
  <wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Dayanand]]></wp:author_last_name>
</wp:author>
<wp:category>
  <wp:term_id>1</wp:term_id>
  <wp:category_nicename>uncategorized</wp:category_nicename>
  <wp:category_parent/>
  <wp:cat_name><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></wp:cat_name>
</wp:category>
<generator>http://wordpress.com/</generator>
<image>
		<url>http://s0.wp.com/i/buttonw-com.png</url>
		<title>Quantum Computing</title>
		<link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com</link>
	</image>
	<item>
  <title><![CDATA[About]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/about/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:36:33 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/?page_id=1</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[This is an example of a page. Unlike posts, which are displayed on your blog’s front page in the order they’re published, pages are better suited for more timeless content that you want to be easily accessible, like your About or Contact information. Click the Edit link to make changes to this page or <a title="Direct link to Add New Page in your Dashboard" href="https://wordpress.com/page/219238261/new/">add another page</a>.]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>1</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 14:36:33</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:36:33</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-20 14:36:33</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-20 14:36:33</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>about</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[default]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Custom Styles]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/wp-global-styles-pub%2flivro/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:37:18 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/wp-global-styles-pub%2flivro/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[{"version":2,"isGlobalStylesUserThemeJSON":true}]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>2</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 22:37:18</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:37:18</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-20 22:37:18</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-20 14:37:18</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>wp-global-styles-pub%2flivro</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>wp_global_styles</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="wp_theme" nicename="livro"><![CDATA[livro]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Chapter One]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/?p=3</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:32:21 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/chapter-one/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>The studio was filled with the rich odour of roses, and when the light summer wind stirred amidst the trees of the garden, there came through the open door the heavy scent of the lilac, or the more delicate perfume of the pink-flowering thorn.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>From the corner of the divan of Persian saddle-bags on which he was lying, smoking, as was his custom, innumerable cigarettes, Lord Henry Wotton could just catch the gleam of the honey-sweet and honey-coloured blossoms of a laburnum, whose tremulous branches seemed hardly able to bear the burden of a beauty so flamelike as theirs; and now and then the fantastic shadows of birds in flight flitted across the long tussore-silk curtains that were stretched in front of the huge window, producing a kind of momentary Japanese effect, and making him think of those pallid, jade-faced painters of Tokyo who, through the medium of an art that is necessarily immobile, seek to convey the sense of swiftness and motion. The sullen murmur of the bees shouldering their way through the long unmown grass, or circling with monotonous insistence round the dusty gilt horns of the straggling woodbine, seemed to make the stillness more oppressive. The dim roar of London was like the bourdon note of a distant organ.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>In the centre of the room, clamped to an upright easel, stood the full-length portrait of a young man of extraordinary personal beauty, and in front of it, some little distance away, was sitting the artist himself, Basil Hallward, whose sudden disappearance some years ago caused, at the time, such public excitement and gave rise to so many strange conjectures.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>As the painter looked at the gracious and comely form he had so skilfully mirrored in his art, a smile of pleasure passed across his face, and seemed about to linger there. But he suddenly started up, and closing his eyes, placed his fingers upon the lids, as though he sought to imprison within his brain some curious dream from which he feared he might awake.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“It is your best work, Basil, the best thing you have ever done,” said Lord Henry languidly. “You must certainly send it next year to the Grosvenor. The Academy is too large and too vulgar. Whenever I have gone there, there have been either so many people that I have not been able to see the pictures, which was dreadful, or so many pictures that I have not been able to see the people, which was worse. The Grosvenor is really the only place.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“I don’t think I shall send it anywhere,” he answered, tossing his head back in that odd way that used to make his friends laugh at him at Oxford. “No, I won’t send it anywhere.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Lord Henry elevated his eyebrows and looked at him in amazement through the thin blue wreaths of smoke that curled up in such fanciful whorls from his heavy, opium-tainted cigarette. “Not send it anywhere? My dear fellow, why? Have you any reason? What odd chaps you painters are! You do anything in the world to gain a reputation. As soon as you have one, you seem to want to throw it away. It is silly of you, for there is only one thing in the world worse than being talked about, and that is not being talked about. A portrait like this would set you far above all the young men in England, and make the old men quite jealous, if old men are ever capable of any emotion.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“I know you will laugh at me,” he replied, “but I really can’t exhibit it. I have put too much of myself into it.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Lord Henry stretched himself out on the divan and laughed.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Yes, I knew you would; but it is quite true, all the same.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Too much of yourself in it! Upon my word, Basil, I didn’t know you were so vain; and I really can’t see any resemblance between you, with your rugged strong face and your coal-black hair, and this young Adonis, who looks as if he was made out of ivory and rose-leaves. Why, my dear Basil, he is a Narcissus, and you—well, of course you have an intellectual expression and all that. But beauty, real beauty, ends where an intellectual expression begins. Intellect is in itself a mode of exaggeration, and destroys the harmony of any face. The moment one sits down to think, one becomes all nose, or all forehead, or something horrid. Look at the successful men in any of the learned professions. How perfectly hideous they are! Except, of course, in the Church. But then in the Church they don’t think. A bishop keeps on saying at the age of eighty what he was told to say when he was a boy of eighteen, and as a natural consequence he always looks absolutely delightful. Your mysterious young friend, whose name you have never told me, but whose picture really fascinates me, never thinks. I feel quite sure of that. He is some brainless beautiful creature who should be always here in winter when we have no flowers to look at, and always here in summer when we want something to chill our intelligence. Don’t flatter yourself, Basil: you are not in the least like him.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“You don’t understand me, Harry,” answered the artist. “Of course I am not like him. I know that perfectly well. Indeed, I should be sorry to look like him. You shrug your shoulders? I am telling you the truth. There is a fatality about all physical and intellectual distinction, the sort of fatality that seems to dog through history the faltering steps of kings. It is better not to be different from one’s fellows. The ugly and the stupid have the best of it in this world. They can sit at their ease and gape at the play. If they know nothing of victory, they are at least spared the knowledge of defeat. They live as we all should live—undisturbed, indifferent, and without disquiet. They neither bring ruin upon others, nor ever receive it from alien hands. Your rank and wealth, Harry; my brains, such as they are—my art, whatever it may be worth; Dorian Gray’s good looks—we shall all suffer for what the gods have given us, suffer terribly.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Dorian Gray? Is that his name?” asked Lord Henry, walking across the studio towards Basil Hallward.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Yes, that is his name. I didn’t intend to tell it to you.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>3</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 22:32:21</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:32:21</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-22 23:10:49</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-22 15:10:49</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>chapter-one__trashed</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>trash</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>sharing_disabled</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>switch_like_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_hs_old_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[21]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_trash_meta_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_trash_meta_time</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1684768249]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_desired_post_slug</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[chapter-one]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Chapter Two]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/?p=4</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:32:20 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/chapter-two/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Oh, I can’t explain. When I like people immensely, I never tell their names to any one. It is like surrendering a part of them. I have grown to love secrecy. It seems to be the one thing that can make modern life mysterious or marvellous to us. The commonest thing is delightful if one only hides it. When I leave town now I never tell my people where I am going. If I did, I would lose all my pleasure. It is a silly habit, I dare say, but somehow it seems to bring a great deal of romance into one’s life. I suppose you think me awfully foolish about it?”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Not at all,” answered Lord Henry, “not at all, my dear Basil. You seem to forget that I am married, and the one charm of marriage is that it makes a life of deception absolutely necessary for both parties. I never know where my wife is, and my wife never knows what I am doing. When we meet—we do meet occasionally, when we dine out together, or go down to the Duke’s—we tell each other the most absurd stories with the most serious faces. My wife is very good at it—much better, in fact, than I am. She never gets confused over her dates, and I always do. But when she does find me out, she makes no row at all. I sometimes wish she would; but she merely laughs at me.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“I hate the way you talk about your married life, Harry,” said Basil Hallward, strolling towards the door that led into the garden. “I believe that you are really a very good husband, but that you are thoroughly ashamed of your own virtues. You are an extraordinary fellow. You never say a moral thing, and you never do a wrong thing. Your cynicism is simply a pose.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“Being natural is simply a pose, and the most irritating pose I know,” cried Lord Henry, laughing; and the two young men went out into the garden together and ensconced themselves on a long bamboo seat that stood in the shade of a tall laurel bush. The sunlight slipped over the polished leaves. In the grass, white daisies were tremulous.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>After a pause, Lord Henry pulled out his watch. “I am afraid I must be going, Basil,” he murmured, “and before I go, I insist on your answering a question I put to you some time ago.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“What is that?” said the painter, keeping his eyes fixed on the ground.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“You know quite well.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>“I do not, Harry.”</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>4</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 22:32:20</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:32:20</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-22 23:10:46</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-22 15:10:46</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>chapter-two__trashed</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>trash</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>sharing_disabled</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>switch_like_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_hs_old_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[23]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_trash_meta_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[publish]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_trash_meta_time</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1684768246]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_desired_post_slug</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[chapter-two]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Contact]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/contact/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:32:19 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/contact/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:group {"align":"wide"} -->
<div class="wp-block-group alignwide"><!-- wp:heading {"level":1} -->
<h1 id="contact-1">Contact</h1>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:columns -->
<div class="wp-block-columns"><!-- wp:column {"width":""} -->
<div class="wp-block-column"><!-- wp:paragraph {"fontSize":"small"} -->
<p class="has-small-font-size">The studio was filled with the rich odour of roses, and when the light summer wind stirred amidst the trees of the garden.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:group {"style":{"spacing":{"padding":{"top":"1em","bottom":"2em"}}}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group" style="padding-top:1em;padding-bottom:2em"><!-- wp:buttons -->
<div class="wp-block-buttons"><!-- wp:button {"style":{"spacing":{"padding":{"top":"1em","right":"1em","bottom":"1em","left":"1em"}}},"fontSize":"x-small"} -->
<div class="wp-block-button has-custom-font-size has-x-small-font-size"><a class="wp-block-button__link" style="padding-top:1em;padding-right:1em;padding-bottom:1em;padding-left:1em">Get in Touch</a></div>
<!-- /wp:button --></div>
<!-- /wp:buttons --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->

<!-- wp:spacer {"height":"16px"} -->
<div style="height:16px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>
<!-- /wp:spacer --></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column -->
<div class="wp-block-column"><!-- wp:image {"id":34,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none","className":"size-large"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://livrodemo.files.wordpress.com/2022/01/9b5c1-chair.jpg?w=731" alt="" class="wp-image-34" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image --></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"verticalAlignment":"bottom","width":""} -->
<div class="wp-block-column is-vertically-aligned-bottom"><!-- wp:paragraph {"align":"right","fontSize":"small"} -->
<p class="has-text-align-right has-small-font-size"><em>Follow us:</em></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:social-links {"iconColor":"secondary","iconColorValue":"var(u002du002dwpu002du002dpresetu002du002dcoloru002du002dsecondary)","className":"is-style-logos-only","layout":{"type":"flex","justifyContent":"right"}} -->
<ul class="wp-block-social-links has-icon-color is-style-logos-only"><!-- wp:social-link {"url":"#","service":"twitter"} /-->

<!-- wp:social-link {"url":"#","service":"facebook"} /-->

<!-- wp:social-link {"url":"#","service":"instagram"} /--></ul>
<!-- /wp:social-links --></div>
<!-- /wp:column --></div>
<!-- /wp:columns --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>5</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 22:32:19</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:32:19</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-20 22:32:19</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-20 14:32:19</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>contact</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_headstart_post</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[_hs_extra]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>sharing_disabled</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>switch_like_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_hs_old_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[28]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wpas_skip_all_services</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[header-footer-only]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_checklist_post_type</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[_hs_extra]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[About]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/about-2/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:32:18 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/about-2/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:group {"align":"wide"} -->
<div class="wp-block-group alignwide"><!-- wp:heading {"level":1} -->
<h1 id="about-1">About</h1>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:columns -->
<div class="wp-block-columns"><!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"><!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 id="felicia-gonalez-1">Felicia Gonalez</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph {"fontSize":"small"} -->
<p class="has-small-font-size">The studio was filled with the rich odour of roses, and when the light summer wind stirred amidst the trees of the garden, there came through the open door the heavy scent of the lilac, or the more delicate perfume of the pink-flowering thorn.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"><!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 id="ebony-james-1">Ebony James</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph {"fontSize":"small"} -->
<p class="has-small-font-size">In the centre of the room, clamped to an upright easel, stood the full-length portrait of a young man of extraordinary personal beauty, and in front of it, some little distance away, was sitting the artist himself, Basil Hallward.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"></div>
<!-- /wp:column --></div>
<!-- /wp:columns -->

<!-- wp:spacer {"height":"16px"} -->
<div style="height:16px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>
<!-- /wp:spacer -->

<!-- wp:columns -->
<div class="wp-block-columns"><!-- wp:column {"width":""} -->
<div class="wp-block-column"></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"66.66%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:66.66%"><!-- wp:image {"id":30,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"none","className":"size-full"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large size-full"><img src="https://livrodemo.files.wordpress.com/2022/01/4eea5-writing.jpg?w=1024" alt="" class="wp-image-30" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image --></div>
<!-- /wp:column --></div>
<!-- /wp:columns -->

<!-- wp:spacer {"height":"16px"} -->
<div style="height:16px" aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"></div>
<!-- /wp:spacer -->

<!-- wp:columns -->
<div class="wp-block-columns"><!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"><!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 id="matthew-porter-1">Matthew Porter</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph {"fontSize":"small"} -->
<p class="has-small-font-size">In the centre of the room, clamped to an upright easel, stood the full-length portrait of a young man of extraordinary personal beauty, and in front of it, some little distance away, was sitting the artist himself, Basil Hallward.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"></div>
<!-- /wp:column --></div>
<!-- /wp:columns -->

<!-- wp:columns -->
<div class="wp-block-columns"><!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"></div>
<!-- /wp:column -->

<!-- wp:column {"width":"33.33%"} -->
<div class="wp-block-column" style="flex-basis:33.33%"><!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 id="vic-desmond-1">Vic Desmond</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph {"fontSize":"small"} -->
<p class="has-small-font-size">The studio was filled with the rich odour of roses, and when the light summer wind stirred amidst the trees of the garden, there came through the open door the heavy scent of the lilac, or the more delicate perfume of the pink-flowering thorn.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></div>
<!-- /wp:column --></div>
<!-- /wp:columns --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>6</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 22:32:18</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:32:18</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-20 22:32:18</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-20 14:32:18</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>about-2</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>page</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_headstart_post</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[_hs_extra]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>sharing_disabled</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>switch_like_status</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:1:{i:0;N;}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_starter_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_hs_old_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[25]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wpas_skip_all_services</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_page_template</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[header-footer-only]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_checklist_post_type</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[_hs_extra]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Application of Quantum computing]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/application-of-quantum-computing/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 15:12:20 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/?p=7</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Proposed Application: Cryptography and Encryption</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><strong>Created By</strong>: </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><strong>Payal</strong> - 20201CAI0122</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><strong> Grace</strong>- 20201CAI0147</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><strong> Mayurikaa</strong> - 20201CAI0112</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:group {"layout":{"type":"constrained"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group"><!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">Introduction:</mark></em></strong></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->

<!-- wp:paragraph {"align":"left"} -->
<p class="has-text-align-left"><em> </em>Quantum computing, a rapidly advancing field at the intersection of quantum physics and computer science, offers the promise of solving complex problems that classical computers struggle with. However, it is crucial to approach the topic with caution, avoiding bold claims and pseudoscience. In this blog post, we will examine a proposed application of quantum computing, explore the potential advantages it may bring, and outline the required performance metrics for achieving these advantages.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">Cryptography and Encryption</mark></em></strong>:</h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>One area where quantum computing holds significant promise is in the field of cryptography and encryption. Cryptographic systems, which ensure secure communication and data protection, rely on complex mathematical problems that are currently difficult to crack using classical computing methods. Quantum computers have the potential to revolutionize cryptography by leveraging their unique properties to solve these problems more efficiently.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">Classical To Quantum : </mark></em></strong><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color"><strong><em>Cryptography</em></strong></mark></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:gallery {"linkTo":"none"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-gallery has-nested-images columns-default is-cropped"><!-- wp:image {"id":29,"sizeSlug":"large","linkDestination":"custom"} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img src="https://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p11.jpg?w=1024" alt="" class="wp-image-29" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image --></figure>
<!-- /wp:gallery -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">Advantages of Quantum Computing in Cryptography:</mark></em></strong></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline"><strong>Breaking Classical Encryption</strong>:</span> Quantum computers can employ Shor's algorithm, a quantum algorithm capable of factoring large numbers exponentially faster than classical algorithms. This ability poses a significant threat to classical encryption methods, such as the widely used RSA algorithm. With quantum computing, cryptographic systems that currently guarantee security could be vulnerable, prompting the need for new encryption techniques designed to withstand quantum attacks.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Quantum-Safe Cryptography:</span></strong> Quantum computing can also provide solutions for quantum-safe or post-quantum cryptography. Researchers are actively developing cryptographic algorithms that are resistant to attacks by both classical and quantum computers. By harnessing the power of quantum computing, we can develop encryption methods that are secure against potential future advancements in quantum technology, ensuring the longevity of secure communication.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><span style="text-decoration: underline"><strong>Enhanced Key Distribution</strong>:</span> Quantum computing offers the potential for secure key distribution through quantum key distribution (QKD) protocols. QKD utilizes quantum properties, such as the principle of entanglement, to enable the secure exchange of cryptographic keys between two parties. This provides a higher level of security and protection against eavesdropping attacks.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Faster Cryptographic Operations:</span></strong> Quantum computers can accelerate various cryptographic operations, such as hashing and symmetric key generation. This speedup can have practical applications in areas where real-time encryption and decryption are essential, such as secure communication networks and financial transactions.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Unforgeable Digital Signatures: </span></strong>Quantum computing can offer advancements in digital signature schemes. Quantum-resistant signature schemes, such as the ones based on lattice-based cryptography or code-based cryptography, can provide secure and unforgeable digital signatures even in the presence of powerful quantum computers. This ensures the integrity and authenticity of digital documents and transactions.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Improved Cryptanalysis: </span></strong>Quantum computing can enhance cryptanalysis techniques by enabling more efficient and powerful algorithms for breaking cryptographic schemes. This can be beneficial in scenarios where there is a need to analyze and assess the security of existing cryptographic protocols and systems. By identifying vulnerabilities, quantum computing can drive the development of stronger and more resilient cryptographic algorithms.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color"><strong><em>Performance Requirements for Quantum Advantage</em>:</strong></mark></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p><strong>To achieve the advantages of quantum computing in cryptography, several performance requirements must be met:</strong></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Qubit Count:</span></strong> Quantum computers need a sufficient number of qubits to perform the required computations. For example, to break commonly used RSA encryption, thousands or even millions of qubits would be necessary. The scalability of quantum systems is a critical factor, and the technology must advance to accommodate the qubit counts required for practical applications.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Error Correction and Gate Fidelity:</span></strong> Quantum computers are prone to errors caused by decoherence and noise. To achieve reliable results, error correction techniques must be implemented, and gate fidelities must be high to minimize computational errors. Continuous advancements in error correction and noise reduction will be necessary to ensure the accuracy and reliability of quantum computations.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:list -->
<ul><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Quantum Error Correction</span></strong>: Quantum computers are susceptible to errors caused by quantum decoherence and noise. To achieve the necessary reliability for practical applications, robust quantum error correction techniques must be developed and implemented. Error correction is crucial for maintaining the integrity of quantum information during computations and improving the overall accuracy of quantum algorithms.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Longer Coherence Times:</span></strong> Coherence time refers to the duration during which quantum information can be reliably stored and manipulated in a quantum system. To perform complex cryptographic computations, quantum computers need longer coherence times to minimize errors and increase the accuracy of the results. Advancements in hardware and error mitigation techniques are required to extend coherence times and improve the overall performance of quantum systems.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Scalable Quantum Architectures:</span></strong> Quantum computers must be built with scalable architectures to accommodate the increasing complexity of cryptographic computations. The ability to add more qubits and connect them effectively is crucial for tackling larger-scale cryptographic problems. Developing scalable quantum architectures will enable practical applications of quantum cryptography and ensure the computational power needed for breaking classical encryption or implementing quantum-safe cryptographic schemes.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong><span style="text-decoration: underline">Improved Qubit Fidelity:</span></strong> Qubit fidelity refers to the accuracy and reliability of individual qubits in a quantum computer. Higher qubit fidelity reduces computational errors and improves the overall performance of quantum algorithms. Advancements in qubit fabrication, error correction techniques, and noise reduction methods are necessary to achieve the required qubit fidelity for practical cryptographic applications.</li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ul>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">Let Us Find The codes below for the </mark></em></strong><font color="#519c70"><b><i>follow</i></b></font><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">ing:</mark></em></strong></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:list {"ordered":true} -->
<ol><!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong>implementation of gates</strong></li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li> <strong>Breaking classical encryption</strong></li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong>Quantum-safe Cryptography</strong></li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li> <strong>Qubit count</strong></li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong>error correction</strong></li>
<!-- /wp:list-item -->

<!-- wp:list-item -->
<li><strong>Simple circu</strong>it <strong>for QKD protocol</strong></li>
<!-- /wp:list-item --></ol>
<!-- /wp:list -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><span style="text-decoration: underline"><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">Find The Codes Below:</mark></span></em></strong></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph {"align":"justify"} -->
<p class="has-text-align-justify">1st-https://github.com/Payal-1607/Quantum-Mini-Project/blob/a5cace3205d3deaa9c055659f96541cdabcd70b4/link1.ipynb</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>2nd- 5th - https://github.com/Payal-1607/Quantum-Mini-Project/blob/a5cace3205d3deaa9c055659f96541cdabcd70b4/codes.ipynb</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>6th -    https://github.com/Payal-1607/Quantum-Mini-Project/blob/a5cace3205d3deaa9c055659f96541cdabcd70b4/list%206.ipynb</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:heading -->
<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong><em><mark style="background-color:rgba(0, 0, 0, 0);color:#519c70" class="has-inline-color">CONCLUSION :</mark></em></strong></h2>
<!-- /wp:heading -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Quantum computing has the potential to revolutionize the field of cryptography and encryption, both by breaking classical encryption methods and by providing quantum-safe cryptographic solutions. However, it is essential to remain grounded in realistic expectations, acknowledging the current limitations of quantum technology. As the field progresses, advancements in qubit count, error correction, and gate fidelity will be crucial for harnessing the advantages of quantum computing in cryptography. By treading carefully and focusing on rigorous scientific research, we can unlock the true potential of quantum computing while guarding against unsubstantiated claims and pseudoscience.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>7</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 23:12:20</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 15:12:20</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-29 21:57:44</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-29 13:57:44</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>open</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>application-of-quantum-computing</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_jetpack_post_was_ever_published</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_last_editor_used_jetpack</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[block-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>timeline_notification</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1685368667]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_job_id</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[84460384913]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_oembed_9866d1027e82831ecc9386955a425b1e</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{{unknown}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>wordads_ufa</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[s:wpcom-ufa-v3-beta:1685368799]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Navigation]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/navigation/</link>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 14:41:08 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/navigation/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:page-list /-->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>9</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-20 22:41:08</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-20 14:41:08</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-20 22:41:08</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-20 14:41:08</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>navigation</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>wp_navigation</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[p1]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/application-of-quantum-computing/p1/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 04:23:37 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p1.gif</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>24</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-23 12:23:37</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-23 04:23:37</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-23 12:23:37</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-23 04:23:37</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>p1</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>7</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>https://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p1.gif</wp:attachment_url>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/8da/219238261/files/2023/05/p1.gif]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:6:{s:5:"width";i:2384;s:6:"height";i:1684;s:4:"file";s:79:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/8da/219238261/files/2023/05/p1.gif";s:8:"filesize";i:691055;s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:1:"0";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:0:"";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:1:"0";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:1:"0";s:3:"iso";s:1:"0";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:1:"0";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"0";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[p1-1]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/application-of-quantum-computing/p1-1/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 04:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p1-1.gif</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>27</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-23 12:28:17</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-23 04:28:17</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-23 12:28:17</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-23 04:28:17</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>p1-1</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>7</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>https://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p1-1.gif</wp:attachment_url>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/8da/219238261/files/2023/05/p1-1.gif]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:6:{s:5:"width";i:2384;s:6:"height";i:1684;s:4:"file";s:81:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/8da/219238261/files/2023/05/p1-1.gif";s:8:"filesize";i:691055;s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:1:"0";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:0:"";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:1:"0";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:1:"0";s:3:"iso";s:1:"0";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:1:"0";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"0";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[p11]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/20/application-of-quantum-computing/p11/</link>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 04:32:04 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">http://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p11.jpg</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>29</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-23 12:32:04</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-23 04:32:04</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-23 12:32:04</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-23 04:32:04</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>open</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>p11</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>inherit</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>7</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>attachment</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <wp:attachment_url>https://researchpaper8.files.wordpress.com/2023/05/p11.jpg</wp:attachment_url>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_attached_file</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/8da/219238261/files/2023/05/p11.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_wp_attachment_metadata</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[a:6:{s:5:"width";i:2384;s:6:"height";i:1444;s:4:"file";s:80:"/home/wpcom/public_html/wp-content/blogs.dir/8da/219238261/files/2023/05/p11.jpg";s:8:"filesize";i:1695750;s:5:"sizes";a:0:{}s:10:"image_meta";a:12:{s:8:"aperture";s:1:"0";s:6:"credit";s:0:"";s:6:"camera";s:0:"";s:7:"caption";s:0:"";s:17:"created_timestamp";s:10:"1684834816";s:9:"copyright";s:0:"";s:12:"focal_length";s:1:"0";s:3:"iso";s:1:"0";s:13:"shutter_speed";s:1:"0";s:5:"title";s:0:"";s:11:"orientation";s:1:"1";s:8:"keywords";a:0:{}}}]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
<item>
  <title><![CDATA[Header]]></title>
  <link>https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/29/header/</link>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 13:56:48 +0000</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>payaldayanand26</dc:creator>
  <guid isPermaLink="false">https://researchpaper8.wordpress.com/2023/05/29/header/</guid>
  <description/>
  <content:encoded><![CDATA[<!-- wp:group {"align":"full","style":{"spacing":{"padding":{"bottom":"var(\u002d\u002dwp\u002d\u002dcustom\u002d\u002dspacing\u002d\u002dlarge, 10rem)","top":"var(\u002d\u002dwp\u002d\u002dcustom\u002d\u002dspacing\u002d\u002dsmall, 1.25rem)"}}},"layout":{"type":"flex","justifyContent":"left"}} -->
<div class="wp-block-group alignfull" style="padding-top:var(--wp--custom--spacing--small, 1.25rem);padding-bottom:var(--wp--custom--spacing--large, 10rem)"><!-- wp:navigation {"ref":9,"overlayMenu":"always","overlayBackgroundColor":"background","overlayTextColor":"foreground","layout":{"type":"flex","setCascadingProperties":true,"justifyContent":"left"},"style":{"typography":{"fontStyle":"normal","fontWeight":"300"}},"fontSize":"x-large"} /-->

<!-- wp:site-title {"style":{"spacing":{"padding":{"top":"0.35ch"}},"typography":{"textTransform":"uppercase"}}} /-->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph --></div>
<!-- /wp:group -->]]></content:encoded>
  <excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
  <wp:post_id>50</wp:post_id>
  <wp:post_date>2023-05-29 21:56:48</wp:post_date>
  <wp:post_date_gmt>2023-05-29 13:56:48</wp:post_date_gmt>
  <wp:post_modified>2023-05-29 21:56:48</wp:post_modified>
  <wp:post_modified_gmt>2023-05-29 13:56:48</wp:post_modified_gmt>
  <wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
  <wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
  <wp:post_name>header</wp:post_name>
  <wp:status>publish</wp:status>
  <wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
  <wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
  <wp:post_type>wp_template_part</wp:post_type>
  <wp:post_password/>
  <wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
  <category domain="wp_template_part_area" nicename="header"><![CDATA[header]]></category>
  <category domain="wp_theme" nicename="livro"><![CDATA[livro]]></category>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>origin</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[theme]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
  <wp:postmeta>
    <wp:meta_key>_publicize_pending</wp:meta_key>
    <wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
  </wp:postmeta>
</item>
  </channel>
</rss>
